Unyime Emmanuel

Lagos, Nigeria

unyimeemmanuel012@gmail.com

07066261517

https://unyime.vercel.app/

Summary

I'm a prolific web developer with a passion for data structures and beating former "best yets". I create responsive and interactive websites that are SEO-friendly, thus decreasing overall access issues by 90% and increasing user experience by 60%. Constantly receive high user experience scores for all web development projects like the ones done on frontendentor. Passionate about building web apps with implementation of object-oriented and functional programming.

Experience



Web Developer

Haqqman

Mar 2022 - Present (2 months +)

React Developer(NextJs)

Yefepere

Dec 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

Frontend Web Developer

1938&Co

Mar 2020 - Jun 2020 (4 months)

Education



University of Uyo

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Chemical Technology/Technician 2019 - 2023

Licenses & Certifications



(A) Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

Skills

Front-End Development • Web Development • Responsive Web Design • User Interface Design • React.js • PHP • Laravel • jQuery • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)